photosig.com 2012-05-05

# photoSIG » Privacy Policy

SIG Networks Corporation is committed to protecting your privacy. You can visit most pages on our site without giving us any information about yourself. However, sometimes we do need information to provide services, and this privacy policy explains data collection and use in those situations. 

### Collection of your Personal Information

We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (personal information) or allows us to contact you. Personal information collected by SIG Networks Corporation ("SNC") is limited to your name, e-mail address, and location. All the information we collect from you will be for statistical and demographic purposes only. We will not give out your information or sell it to others. Further, we will not send you unsolicited email or "spam." The only things we email you will be things you explicitly request (like a password reminder), mailing lists that you asked to receive, or notifications about your account status. 

### Use of your Personal Information

Your email address is collected in order to have an address to send you lost password notifications. Also, collecting this information serves as a way to limit abuse of the system, as it helps us detect duplicate or "shill" accounts. Your email address is never displayed publicly unless you send someone an invitation ("Tell a Friend") or a message through the photoSIG internal mail system, in which case your email address will be displayed to the recipient so that he or she may reply directly. 

We will only send you mail once when you create your account, and then only when you request a lost password to be sent to you. Also, we may send you mail from photoSIG and our partners if you have checked the "Allow email from photoSIG and partners" option in your user profile. 

We require that you provide your account name or "handle" to be listed with your submissions. We also require that you provide your real first and last names. Your account name and first name are displayed throughout the system alongside your contributions and in the User Directory and Who's On pages. Your last name is never displayed but is needed to help us understand and keep track of who is using our system. 

We ask for your city, state, zip code, and country, for our own statistical purposes. We will never display this information on the site, unless you select the "Show my city and state in my public profile" in your user profile. You can optionally enter your website's URL or other information about yourself in your user profile. If you list this information, it will show up your public user information page. 

You may optionally provide us with your street address and telephone number. We may use this information to contact you in the unlikely event that we need to get in touch and your email address is not working. 

SNC may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on SNC or photoSIG; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of SNC and photoSIG, or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of SNC or its designees, users of photoSIG and/or the services associated with photoSIG, or members of the public. 

Your information may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which SNC or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintains facilities, and by using this site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. 

### Control of your Personal Information

When you create an account, or otherwise give us personal information, SNC will not share that information with third parties without your permission, apart from the limited exceptions already listed. Registering also allows you to tell us how or whether you want SNC to communicate with you. We may send out periodic e-mails informing you of technical service or security issues related to the photoSIG or the services provided, or confirming your registration. 

### Access to your Personal Information

We will provide you with the means to ensure that your personal information is correct and current. In the mySIG section of photoSIG, you can view and edit personal information you have already given us and change the options affecting the use and display of your personal information. 

### Security of your Personal Information

SNC is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. 

### Protection of Children's Personal Information

photoSIG does not knowingly collect any personal information from children without parental consent. 

### Use of Cookies

When someone visits photoSIG, a cookie is placed on the visitor's computer (if the visitor accepts cookies) or is read if the visitor has visited the site previously. We use cookies to remember users' session information from page to page. In addition, our advertisers pay place cookies of their own on visitors' computers. Though outside of our control, these cookies are usually used to prevent the advertiser from delivering the same advertisement to the same visitor more than a set number of times. 

If you choose to not have your browser accept cookies from photoSIG, you will be able to view the text on the screens, however you may not experience a personalized visit or not be able to utilize all of the services provided. 

### Enforcement of this Privacy Policy

If you have questions regarding this policy, you should contact SNC by email at [privacy@photosig.com](mailto:privacy@photosig.com). 

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

SNC will occasionally update this privacy privacy. When we do, we will also revise the "last updated" date at the top of the privacy statement. For material changes to this statement, SNC will notify you by placing prominent notice on the Main page. 

photoSIG
